luxurywatchexchange.com 2015-12-22

# Luxury Watch Exchange | Auction Sell Buy Trade

  * Forum

**PRIVACY POLICY** ** **

**Introdution**

Luxury Watch Exchange is a Limited Libility Company, and corporate headquarters in Sun Valley, CA. We own and operate an auction site specializing in the exchange of luxury timepieces. We are committed to protecting any data that we collect concerning you.  By using our services you agree to the use of the data that we collect in accordance with this Privacy Policy. **We are committed to protecting your privacy.** We collect the minimum amount of information about you necessary to provide you with satisfactory service. This Policy indicates the processes that may result in data being collected about you. Your use of this website confers upon us the right to collect that information. 

**Information Collected:**  We may collect any or all of the information that you give us depending on the type of transaction you enter into, including your name, address, telephone number, fax number, bank accounts, PayPal information, credit card information and email address, together with data about your use of the website.  Other information that may be needed from time to time to process a request may also be collected as indicated on the website.

Data in relation to credit card payments are processed by Authorize.net and Paypal on a secure website linked to ours and they have their own privacy policies.

**Information Use:**  We use the information collected primarily to process the task for which you visited the website.  All reasonable precautions are taken to prevent unauthorised access to this information.  This safeguard may require you to provide additional forms of identity should you wish to obtain information about your account details.

  **Cookies:** Your Internet browser has the in-built facility for storing small files - "cookies" - that hold information which allows a website to recognise your account.  Our website takes advantage of this facility to enhance your experience. You have the ability to prevent your computer from accepting cookies but if you do certain functionality on the website may be impaired.   

**Disclosing Information:**  We **do not disclose** any personal information obtained about you from this website to third parties except when we need to do so in order to complete the transaction – e.g. when arranging for a courier company to deliver goods that you have ordered.  We may also use the information to keep in contact with you and inform you of developments associated with our business. You will be given the opportunity to remove yourself from any mailing list or similar device. If at any time in the future we should wish to disclose information collected on this website to any third party, it would only be with your knowledge and consent. We may from time to time provide information of a general nature to third parties - for example, the number of individuals visiting our website or completing a registration form, but we will not use any information that could identify those individuals.   

**Changes to this Policy:**  Any changes to our Privacy Policy will be placed here and will supersede this version of our Policy. We will take reasonable steps to draw your attention to any changes in our Policy. However, to be on the safe side, we suggest that you read this document each time you use the website to ensure that it continues to meet with your approval. **Contacting Us: **If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, or if you want to know what information we have collected about you, please email us at [admin@uxurywatchexchange.com](mailto:admin@theluxurywatchexchange.com).  You can also correct any factual errors in that information or request us to remove your details form any list under our control.

_**Watch News!     Internet freedom around the world has declined for the **_

_**                           fifth consecutive year, with more governments censoring**_

_**                           information of public interest and placing greater demands**_

_**                           on the private sector to take down offending content. The**_

_**                           goal of these restrictions is usually to protect powerful **_

_**                           figures and the official views on religion or morality that **_

_**                           may undergird leaders' popularity using legal USA shipping **_

_**                           services.   **__** [ **Freedom House Net Report**](https://freedomhouse.org/report/freedom-net/freedom-net-2015)**_

_**                           Chinese Police Luxury Watch Corruption!  For several years**_

_**                          corrupt officials have been buying.  Police officials have been**_

_**                         illegally smuggling.  Huge amounts of stolen items from USA**_

_**                          using legal USA shipping services.   **__** [ **Luxury Watch Corruption**](https://www.google.com/?gws_rd=ssl#q=chinese+police+luxury+watch+corruption)**_

_**                             _**Luxury Watch Corruption was big $$$ on 'DarkNet' too!   The**_**_

_**_**                         FBI destroyed the 'Silk Road' which caused a huge problem for**_**_

_**_**                         sellers of stolen items to corrupt buyers.    **_**_[**FBI**](http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/10/21/fbi-cracks-silk-road/2984921/)

                                     _**_**Hyper-accurate atomic clock won't lose a second in 15 billion years!     **_**_[**Atomic Clock**](http://www.latimes.com/science/sciencenow/la-sci-sn-new-best-atomic-clock-yet-20150420-story.html)

_**_**                         Gold plated Apple Watch or Buy with diamonds sometimes for **_**_

_**_**                         more than $100K!     **_**_[**Apple Watch**](http://www.latimes.com/business/technology/la-fi-tn-apple-watch-jewelers-20150507-story.html)

_**_**                        Chinese Banks a haven for Web counterfeiters!  **_**_**      **[**Chinese Banks**](http://www.latimes.com/business/la-fi-china-banks-counterfeiting-20150511-story.html)

_**_**Search Engines     **_**_

_**[AOL    ](http://www.aol.com/)[ASK    ](http://www.ask.com/)[BING    ](http://www.bing.com/)[BLEKKO    ](http://www.blekko.com/)[ ](http://www.dogpile.com/)[DUCKDUCKGO    ](http://www.duckduckgo.com/)[GOOGLE    ](http://www.google.com/)[YAHOO](http://www.yahoo.com/)**_

_**

_**Links To Several Luxury Watch Exchange Details & Info**_

**_

_**_**BING     [Watch Auctions    ](http://www.bing.com/search?q=Luxury+Watch+Auctions&FORM=R5FD7) [Watch Exchange    ](http://www.bing.com/search?q=watch+exchange&qs=n&form=QBLH&pq=watch+exchange&sc=7-14&sp=-1&sk=&cvid=878ef5f5abdc40d0934f236bcf7c641a)[Luxury Watch Exchange    ](http://www.bing.com/search?q=watch+exchange&qs=n&form=QBLH&pq=watch+exchange&sc=7-14&sp=-1&sk=&cvid=878ef5f5abdc40d0934f236bcf7c641a) [Wristwatch Auctions ](http://www.bing.com/search?q=wristwatch+auctions&qs=n&form=QBLH&pq=wristwatch+auctions&sc=4-19&sp=-1&sk=&cvid=42eee1d70c5840cc8ae129e08592543a)  **_**_

_**_**GOOGLE     [Rolex](https://www.google.com/search?q=LuxuryWatchExchange.com%2FRolex)**_**_

_**_**AOL    [Auction Luxury Watches    ](http://search.aol.com/aol/search?enabled_terms=&s_it=comsearch&q=Auction+Luxury+Watches/luxurywatchexchange)[Exchange Luxury Watches    ](http://search.aol.com/aol/search?s_it=topsearchbox.search&v_t=comsearch&q=Exchange+Luxury+Watches/luxurywatchexchange)[Luxury Watches Classified    ](http://search.aol.com/aol/search?s_it=topsearchbox.search&v_t=comsearch&q=Luxury+Watches+Classified/luxurywatchexchange)[Luxury Wristwatches](http://search.aol.com/aol/search?s_it=topsearchbox.search&v_t=comsearch&q=www.exchangeluxurywristwatches%2Fluxurywatchexchange)**_**_

_**_**PINTEREST    [Rolex   ](http://www.pinterest.com/lexchange/rolex/)[Patek Philippe](http://www.pinterest.com/lexchange/patek-philippe/)    [Cartier Watches](https://www.pinterest.com/search/pins/?rs=ac&len=2&q=cartier+watches&term_meta%5B%5D=watches|autocomplete|0)**_**_

_**_**  ASK    [Watch Exchange    ](http://www.ask.com/web?q=watch+exchange&qsrc=364&o=0&l=dir&qo=homepageSearchBox)[Luxury Watch Exchange](http://www.ask.com/web?qsrc=1&o=0&l=dir&q=luxury+watch+exchange&qo=serpSearchTopBox) **_**_

_**_**YAHOO     [Trading Luxury Watches    T](https://search.yahoo.com/search;_ylt=Av3hiUDOurhJ74pY5PwSG8.bvZx4?p=Trading+Luxury+Watches&toggle=1&cop=mss&ei=UTF-8&fr=yfp-t-901&fp=1/luxurywatchexchange)[ourbillon Platinum Perpetual Calenda](http://search.aol.com/aol/search?s_it=topsearchbox.search&v_t=comsearch&q=Tourbillon+Platinum+Perpetual+Calendar/luxurywatchexchange)[r    WristWatch Exchange](https://search.yahoo.com/search;_ylt=Av3hiUDOurhJ74pY5PwSG8.bvZx4?p=wrist+watch+exchange&toggle=1&cop=mss&ei=UTF-8&fr=yfp-t-901&fp=1)**_**_

_**_**Popular Site Links**_**_

_**[AMAZON    ](http://www.amazon.com/)[EBAY    ](http://www.ebay.com/)[PINTEREST](http://www.pinterest.com/)[    ](http://www.ebay.com/)[FACEBOOK    ](http://www.facebook.com/)[GMAIL ](http://www.gmail.com/)[   TWITTER    Y](http://www.twitter.com/)[OUTUBE](http://www.youtube.com/)**_

_**_**SAVE Substantial $$$ By Paying With Bank Transfers Or Making Multi Purchases - Ask Seller!  **_**_

_**_**Clickable Links are FREE to elgible & suitable exchanging websites or annual fee for other watch & luxury websites!  Please email or phone for details!  **_**_

_**_**HotLinks to individual luxuxy item for sale as a vastly discounted price have a small charge.   Please email or phone for details!  
**_**_
